https://www.bobscycle.com/privacy-and-cookie-policy/

OffroadMens Riding GearBootsCompression ApparelGlovesGoggles & AccessoriesHealth & FitnessHelmetsJacketsJerseysMX SocksPantsProtective GearWomens Riding GearBootsGlovesGoggles & AccessoriesHealth & FitnessHelmetsJerseysMX SocksPantsProtective GearYouth Riding GearBootsGlovesGoggles & AccessoriesHelmetsJerseysMX SocksPantsProtective GearPartsATV / UTV PartsBody Parts & AccessoriesBolt KitsBrakesChemicals & OilsDriveChain AdjustersEngineBearingsExhaustExhaust AccessoriesFuel & AirGraphics & SeatsHandlebars & ControlSuspensionTires & WheelsAccessoriesATV / UTV AccessoriesBooksBike StandsCameras & AccessoriesDVDsGas CansGear Bags & PacksDrink SystemsHour MetersPit BoardsShop AccessoriesService ManualsToolsToysTrailer & TransportMore AccessoriesStreetMens Riding GearBootsGlovesEyewearHead WrapsHelmetsJackets & VestsPants & ChapsProtective GearRace SuitsRain WearWomens Riding GearBootsGlovesEyewearHead WrapsHelmetsJackets & VestsPants & ChapsProtective GearRace SuitsRain WearPartsBatteriesBrakesBolt KitsChemicals & OilsElectricalExhaustFuel & AirEngineHandlebars & ControlSuspensionSprockets & ChainsTires & WheelsAccessoriesDVDs & BooksBike StandsBody Parts & AccessoriesCameras & AccessoriesCommunicationCoversCruise Controls & Throttle AssistsGas CansKickstand PadsLightingLocksLuggageMounts, Holders & GPSSeat PadsTank PadsToolsToysTrailer & TransportWindshieldsMore AccessoriesYouth
Riding GearHelmetsCasualMensBeltsFootwearHatsJacketsPantsShirtsShortsSocksSunglassesSweatshirtsUnderwearWalletsWomensFootwearHatsMittens & ScarvesPantsPurses & WalletsShirtsShortsSocksSunglassesSweatshirtsSwimwearYouthHatsJacketsPajamasShirtsShortsSweatshirtsAccessoriesBackpacksHealth & FitnessKeychainsLanyardsPhone CoversStickers / DecalsTowelsWristbandsWater BottlesMore AccessoriesADV / TouringMens Riding GearBootsGlovesHeated GearHelmetsJackets & JerseysPantsWomens Riding GearBootsBase LayersGlovesHeated GearJackets & JerseysPantsPartsBatteriesTires & WheelsTiresAccessoriesCamerasCommunicationLuggage & StorageMounts, Holders & GPSSnowmobileMens Riding GearBibs & PantsBootsGlovesGoggles & AccessoriesHelmetsJacketsMono SuitsProtectionSocksWomens Riding GearBibs & PantsBootsGlovesGoggles & AccessoriesHelmetsJacketsMono SuitsProtectionSocksYouth Riding GearBibs & PantsBootsGlovesGoggles & AccessoriesHelmetsJacketsMono SuitsPartsBodyChemicals & OilsDriveEngine & FuelExhaustHandlebars & ControlService ManualsSuspensionTractionAccessoriesBody WarmersCalendarsCoversDollies & StandsDVDsGearbagsLuggageSafety and SurvivalTow RopesToysTrailer & TransportTools
1-888-306-2627
Privacy and Cookie Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer.
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
CAN-SPAM Compliance
We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.
This policy was last modified on 04/25/2013
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. Bob's Cycle Supply 65 Viking Dr W St Paul, MN 55117 USA 1-800-306-2627
Privacy Policy Customer Pledge
We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives: Federal Trade Commision Fair
California Online Privacy Protection Act
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act
Privacy Alliance
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act
If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form.
